necdisplay.com 2019-04-10

# NEC Display Privacy Policy | NEC Display Website Privacy Information

|  Protecting your privacy is important to NEC Display Solutions of America, Inc. ('NECDisplay Solutions'). We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand this Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. This Privacy Policy applies exclusively to information received from you online and its purpose is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit [ www.necdisplay.com](https://www.necdisplay.com/) ('our Site'), how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, that information.   
---  
Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information. This Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.   
Questions regarding this Policy should be directed to [ privacy.policy@necdisplay.com](mailto:privacy.policy@necdisplay.com) or may also be communicated directly to the following address:   
|   
---  
|  **Customer Information Privacy Practices  
c/o Legal Department **  
---  
NEC Display Solutions of America, Inc.  
3250 Lacey Road, Suite 500  
Downers Grove, Illinois 60515   
Sites Covered By This Statement   
This Online Privacy Statement covers the collection and use of data on the [www.necdisplay.com](https://www.necdisplay.com/) Web site in the United States.   
What Information We Collect   
The information we collect on our Site generally falls into the following two categories: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.   
**Personally Identifiable Information:** This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. The Personally Identifiable Information we collect when you use our Site may include your name, mailing address, phone number, e-mail address, employer, credit card number and its expiration date, shipping address, public postings, prospect email address, and job title. We request Personally Identifiable Information when you order a product or service, participate in certain online promotional activities, fill out online surveys, register a product online, request technical support, and correspond with us. We also collect Personally Identifiable Information when you ask that we send products or information directly to other people; in these cases, we will collect the information you submit about the recipient.   
**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. The non-personally identifiable data we collect when you visit our Site may include the Uniform Resource Locator, i.e. the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web, ("URL") of the Web site that you came from before visiting our Site, which pages you visit on our Site, which URL you next go to, which browser you used to come to our Site, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, and any search terms entered on our Site. This Statement also contains more information about how we use cookies and other technology to collect data.   
Why We Collect Your Information   
Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide customers with superior service and to provide all visitors a smooth, efficient, and personalized experience while using our Site. For example, if you purchase products or supplies, or request information on our Site, we use your Personally Identifiable Information to fill your order or to provide you with the requested information. We may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to analyze customer behavior to help us understand how visitors use our Site and to measure interest in the various pages. We use this information to improve the content of our Site, to make our Site easier to use, and to customize our advertising.   
We do not connect the Personally Identifiable information and Non-Personally identifiable information that we collect on our Site.   
How We Use Your Information   
We gather and use information in a number of ways, including the following:   
**Surfing:** We collect certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information when you visit our Site or click on banner ads for NEC Display Solutions products and services. We collect this information to help run our Site more efficiently, to gather broad demographic information, to monitor the level of activity on our Site, and to evaluate the effectiveness of our advertising. We use cookies and other technology to collect this information.   
**Ordering:** We collect Personally Identifiable Information when you purchase products, supplies or services online. We collect this information to deliver your order, to obtain payment, and to communicate with you about the status of your order.   
**Product registration:** We collect Personally Identifiable Information when you register your NEC products online. We keep this information for reference if you later request customer service and we use the information to personalize that service.   
**Technical support:** We may collect certain information when you request technical support for your NEC products. This information is necessary to identify your systems, understand the configuration of the products, diagnose your questions, and provide solutions.   
**Online surveys and polling:** We collect Personally Identifiable Information from customers who volunteer to complete surveys or participate in polls. We use this information to improve our products and services.   
**Promotional activities/Seminars/Sweepstakes:** We collect Personally Identifiable Information from you when you enter a promotional program or activity, including but not limited to seminars and sweepstakes. We use this information to administer the program or activity, to send you promotional e-mails, notify winners, and make the winners' list publicly available pursuant to certain states' laws.   
**Newsletters and promotional e-mails:** We collect Personally Identifiable Information when you ask us (you "opt-in") to receive newsletters, promotional e-mails, and other information. We use this information to provide you with the information you request.   
**Contact information:** If you contact us, we may keep a record of your correspondence or comments, including Personally Identifiable Information, in a file specific to you. We use this information to help us provide better customer service in the event you contact us again.   
Sharing Your Information   
We only share your Personally Identifiable Information outside the NEC family of companies if it is required by law, or to protect NEC Display Solutions, its customers, or the public, or with companies that help NEC Display Solutions fulfill its obligations with you, and then only with partners who share NEC Display Solutions' commitment to protecting your privacy and data. Except as previously stated, we do not sell, trade, or rent to others the Personally Identifiable Information we collect online. Where NEC Display Solutions engages third parties to perform services on our behalf, we will require them to observe the intent of this Online Privacy Statement.   
Personally Identifiable Information previously collected by NEC Display Solutions may be transferred to any new corporate entity formed as a result of corporate reorganization of NEC Display Solutions, or any of NEC Display Solutions’ divisions, provided that such new corporate entity agrees to abide by the terms of this Privacy Policy.   
From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to a court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release certain Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.   
Your Choices   
NEC Display Solutions will not use or share the Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Site in ways unrelated to the purpose for which you provided the information, including those described in Section titled "How We Use Your Information ", without providing you a choice whether to permit any such unrelated uses. At the time you provide your information, we will offer you a choice as to whether you want to receive ("opt-in") further communications about special offers, product information or other marketing messages. If you choose not to receive these communications ("opt-out"), we will not use the information you provide for this purpose. You can opt out at any time as all e-mail communications from us, such as newsletters, tell you how to stop receiving them. Please follow these instructions if you no longer wish to receive the e-mail messages.   
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.   
Use of Cookies on Our Site   
"Cookies" and "web beacons" are small data files transferred by a Web site to your computer's hard drive. We may use cookies and web beacons when you surf our Site, make purchases, respond to online surveys or polls, or request information. The cookies and web beacons used on our Site do not give us access to your Personally Identifiable Information, but we can use these tools to identify your computer. The information collected permits us to analyze traffic patterns on our Site. This can enable us over time to provide you with a better experience on our Site by improving the content and making it easier to use. For example, cookies and web beacons can keep track of what you have selected to purchase as you continue to shop and allow you to enter your password only once on pages where a logon is required. We may use an agent or third party to implement and manage web beacons on our Site, but information collected by such web beacons will be used only by us.   
Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually refuse cookies, or selectively accept certain cookies, by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If you turn off cookies, though, there may be some features of our Site that will not be available to you and some Web pages may not display properly. You can find information on popular browsers and how you can adjust them to control cookies at the following Web sites:   
Protecting Your Information   
NEC Display Solutions safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.   
NEC Display Solutions uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all Web pages where personal information is required. To make purchases on our Site, you must use an SSL-enabled browser. This protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet.   
In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third-party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order.   
When you access your account information, the information is kept on a secure server. All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access by physical security means.   
Children's privacy   
NEC Display Solutions takes special care to protect the privacy needs of children under the age of 13 and encourages parents to be an active participant in their child's online activities and interests. We abide by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) requirements.   
www.necdisplay.com does not target and is not intended for children under the age of 13. You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site. Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are the parent or guardian of a minor under 18 years of age and believe that they have disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us at [ privacy.policy@necdisplay.com](mailto:privacy.policy@necdisplay.com) so that we may delete the minor's information.   
Links to Third Party Web Sites   
Other sites accessible through our Web site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. NEC Display Solutions is not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Please be aware that this site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to www.necdisplay.com. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Additionally, other companies that place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.   
This Privacy Policy was last changed on March 26, 2003. If NEC Display Solutions makes changes to any terms or conditions of the Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted in this document so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and to whom we will disclose it. We may change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we tell you otherwise.
